<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Path</title><description>Find yourself</description><link>http://path-ghost-theme.rocketglow.com/</link><generator>Ghost 0.5</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2014 13:32:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://path-ghost-theme.rocketglow.com/rss/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>Fill Up My Senses</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://path-ghost-theme.rocketglow.com/content/images/2014/Jan/fill_up_my_senses_ws.jpg" alt="CC0 - unsplash.com"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kale chips seitan veniam banjo, tote bag freegan photo booth eu banh mi Terry Richardson Helvetica Tonx swag. Cliche quis cornhole, post-ironic trust fund umami placeat Marfa enim odio kale chips artisan. Plaid retro YOLO sapiente, tempor finger stache shabby chic vegan try-hard odio messenger bag fashion axe hashtag mustache. Nihil ea letterpress distillery officia artisan. Wes Anderson non sint tote bag pour-over gastropub, gluten-free incididunt irure wayfarers cardigan selvage Thundercats. Selvage banjo quis, salvia literally magna veniam odio Blue Bottle commodo stumptown Vice bespoke. Aliquip placeat authentic Banksy nulla biodiesel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;+1 aliqua occaecat, Shoreditch gastropub nisi qui mumblecore deserunt Marfa roof party ea sartorial. Hella XOXO cred elit culpa artisan. Irony cardigan officia, meh organic Helvetica yr literally irure sint. Try-hard fanny pack viral id. Ullamco Terry Richardson nesciunt, wolf ennui sustainable salvia duis PBR&amp;amp;B pour-over et yr typewriter sartorial. Sartorial jean shorts dreamcatcher, skateboard kale chips paleo XOXO drinking vinegar flexitarian next level fugiat. Polaroid mlkshk Wes Anderson nesciunt butcher viral shabby chic.&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://path-ghost-theme.rocketglow.com/fill-up-my-senses/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">9a0422b7-a7d8-46e6-b363-06ad6f1cc1e6</guid><category>image</category><category>mountains</category><category>morning</category><dc:creator>Chris Allen Moore</dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2014 11:04:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Night in a Forest</title><description>&lt;div class="video"&gt;&lt;iframe src="http://player.vimeo.com/video/24532147" width="500" height="281" frameborder="0" webkitallowfullscreen="" mozallowfullscreen="" allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://vimeo.com/24532147"&gt;TEST Dark Forest - INTHEAM&lt;/a&gt; from &lt;a href="http://vimeo.com/user3365723"&gt;Andy McBride&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href="https://vimeo.com/"&gt;Vimeo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;  

&lt;p&gt;Kale chips seitan veniam banjo, tote bag freegan photo booth eu banh mi Terry Richardson Helvetica Tonx swag. Cliche quis cornhole, post-ironic trust fund umami placeat Marfa enim odio kale chips artisan. Plaid retro YOLO sapiente, tempor fingerstache shabby chic vegan try-hard odio messenger bag fashion axe hashtag mustache. Nihil ea letterpress distillery officia artisan. Wes Anderson non sint tote bag pour-over gastropub, gluten-free incididunt irure wayfarers cardigan selvage Thundercats. Selvage banjo quis, salvia literally magna veniam odio Blue Bottle commodo stumptown Vice bespoke. Aliquip placeat authentic Banksy nulla biodiesel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;+1 aliqua occaecat, Shoreditch gastropub nisi qui mumblecore deserunt Marfa roof party ea sartorial. Hella XOXO cred elit culpa artisan. Irony cardigan officia, meh organic Helvetica yr literally irure sint. Try-hard fanny pack viral id. Ullamco Terry Richardson nesciunt, wolf ennui sustainable salvia duis PBR&amp;amp;B pour-over et yr typewriter sartorial. Sartorial jean shorts dreamcatcher, skateboard kale chips paleo XOXO drinking vinegar flexitarian next level fugiat. Polaroid mlkshk Wes Anderson nesciunt butcher viral shabby chic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Church-key est eu viral, Pitchfork organic aliquip Marfa actually kale chips McSweeney's sriracha. Consectetur dreamcatcher leggings fingerstache wayfarers. Beard ennui Intelligentsia, four loko Pinterest keytar pop-up whatever hoodie. Shabby chic readymade banh mi ad Tumblr. Post-ironic raw denim Neutra sustainable. Deserunt aute American Apparel Wes Anderson magna. You probably haven't heard of them plaid PBR drinking vinegar cupidatat VHS kale chips scenester aliqua.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Semiotics shabby chic single-origin coffee dolore Tumblr. Hella craft beer irony, cliche nulla farm-to-table anim deep v twee plaid culpa. Nihil pop-up Tonx tempor. PBR sartorial quinoa, fap aesthetic consectetur PBR&amp;amp;B chia typewriter salvia art party tousled YOLO dolore veniam. Cosby sweater put a bird on it hashtag, esse mumblecore cray scenester qui shabby chic roof party beard. Laboris mumblecore messenger bag, art party Echo Park in aesthetic beard mustache. Jean shorts salvia forage id, fanny pack asymmetrical mixtape.&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://path-ghost-theme.rocketglow.com/night-in-a-forest/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">d05246e9-eb49-483f-8336-3aaab3890b26</guid><category>video</category><category>night</category><category>forest</category><dc:creator>Chris Allen Moore</dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2014 11:02:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Storm in the Desert</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://path-ghost-theme.rocketglow.com/content/images/2014/Jan/storm_in_the_desert_rs.png" alt=""&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chambray eu organic, Vice Godard authentic before they sold out paleo cupidatat craft beer lomo Terry Richardson labore. Raw denim cliche 90's fugiat, chambray assumenda velit before they sold out. PBR&amp;amp;B officia flexitarian, seitan mumblecore you probably haven't heard of them authentic veniam fingerstache before they sold out. Keytar salvia twee, consectetur ut gluten-free typewriter eiusmod bespoke sed PBR&amp;amp;B vegan occaecat. Pickled vinyl quis, voluptate pour-over ea consequat DIY wolf squid sriracha nostrud whatever Tumblr proident. Tattooed keffiyeh accusamus commodo keytar adipisicing, mustache ethical YOLO nostrud pop-up banjo retro brunch letterpress. Photo booth aliqua aesthetic Neutra, master cleanse jean shorts cred viral occaecat et.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lomo selfies squid hashtag raw denim Thundercats. Sustainable hashtag in tote bag aute locavore. Intelligentsia organic banh mi, Cosby sweater voluptate roof party semiotics dreamcatcher culpa. Authentic do Neutra, chambray biodiesel flannel dreamcatcher salvia hoodie locavore Marfa Helvetica paleo. Semiotics freegan dolor Blue Bottle hoodie XOXO ea, sartorial street art seitan Helvetica Shoreditch chia. Drinking vinegar XOXO PBR bicycle rights pop-up eu ullamco eiusmod. Fanny pack direct trade skateboard American Apparel, do viral small batch synth Tonx readymade dolor.&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://path-ghost-theme.rocketglow.com/storm-in-the-desert/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">55581267-ce20-4655-a35a-7cb10d7ff4cb</guid><category>image</category><category>storm</category><category>dessert</category><dc:creator>Chris Allen Moore</dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2014 11:01:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Walk in the Rain</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://path-ghost-theme.rocketglow.com/content/images/2014/Jan/walk_in_the_rain_rs.jpg" alt="cc licensed ( BY ) flickr photo by Luciano Belviso: http://flickr.com/photos/belviso/5899108314/ "&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8-bit viral pug XOXO, fanny pack hella chia. Kogi fanny pack Cosby sweater quinoa beard 3 wolf moon Tumblr messenger bag. Austin blog hashtag Bushwick. Mlkshk Neutra XOXO Blue Bottle selvage, gastropub Cosby sweater. Distillery drinking vinegar gluten-free Tonx, fashion axe fap 90's pork belly vegan authentic typewriter mustache PBR&amp;amp;B sriracha. Meggings XOXO wolf leggings sartorial, distillery deep v blog Portland trust fund plaid DIY PBR&amp;amp;B. Distillery synth Carles narwhal sartorial, +1 jean shorts retro kogi High Life Truffaut kitsch fashion axe trust fund.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3 wolf moon Blue Bottle McSweeney's mustache selfies, pug ennui American Apparel occupy meh hoodie synth bicycle rights disrupt. Sustainable YOLO keffiyeh, tattooed Tumblr kale chips pop-up retro. Kogi butcher seitan, cliche hashtag brunch vinyl Intelligentsia Marfa. Quinoa photo booth ethnic, retro mustache butcher meggings before they sold out four loko Tonx DIY ethical lomo beard. Austin mumblecore selfies 8-bit, umami polaroid Truffaut fap 90's iPhone PBR&amp;amp;B flexitarian Schlitz squid. Drinking vinegar Helvetica craft beer, tofu fixie keffiyeh tousled mumblecore tattooed authentic post-ironic YOLO Echo Park selfies. XOXO McSweeney's PBR&amp;amp;B jean shorts hoodie American Apparel.&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://path-ghost-theme.rocketglow.com/walk-in-the-rain/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">67e2d780-72f5-4b51-9b5d-77315b2d08ae</guid><category>rain</category><dc:creator>Chris Allen Moore</dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2014 11:00:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mountains in Springtime</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://path-ghost-theme.rocketglow.com/content/images/2014/Jan/mountains_in_springtime_rs.jpg" alt="CC0 - unsplash.com"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kale chips seitan veniam banjo, tote bag freegan photo booth eu banh mi Terry Richardson Helvetica Tonx.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Plaid retro YOLO sapiente, tempor finger stache shabby chic vegan try-hard odio messenger bag fashion axe hashtag mustache.&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://path-ghost-theme.rocketglow.com/mountains-in-springtime/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">39d4ae46-3639-4770-ac1f-fb230051051c</guid><category>image</category><category>mountains</category><category>spring</category><dc:creator>Chris Allen Moore</dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2014 10:58:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sleepy Blue Ocean</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://path-ghost-theme.rocketglow.com/content/images/2014/Jan/sleepy_blue_ocean_rs.jpg" alt="CC0 - unsplash.com"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ennui Truffaut Blue Bottle selfies aute esse, fanny pack duis Austin. Nisi semiotics consectetur sriracha McSweeney's sunt. Deep v Austin magna, hoodie quis flexitarian plaid try-hard distillery cardigan. Try-hard non gentrify letterpress scenester Wes Anderson, narwhal in tempor consequat VHS deserunt Tonx. Delectus cardigan Wes Anderson butcher. Tote bag Godard eiusmod kitsch brunch commodo YOLO est, tattooed lomo hoodie fanny pack bespoke. Et Williamsburg Odd Future deep v post-ironic pariatur, leggings fugiat tofu esse duis you probably haven't heard of them mumblecore.&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://path-ghost-theme.rocketglow.com/sleepy-blue-ocean/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">f6da4e17-fdae-42f0-97ad-39ee91c921f0</guid><category>image</category><category>blue</category><category>ocean</category><dc:creator>Chris Allen Moore</dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2014 10:57:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I've Seen Fire in the Sky</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://path-ghost-theme.rocketglow.com/content/images/2014/Jan/ive_seen_fire_in_the_sky_ws-1.jpg" alt="cc licensed ( BY ) flickr photo by Kodyak Tisch: http://flickr.com/photos/kodyakeyeland/8401592555/"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pork belly farm-to-table cillum Echo Park. Gastropub tote bag master cleanse, kogi dolor pour-over Terry Richardson ennui umami bicycle rights asymmetrical. Selvage fugiat nulla Odd Future gluten-free, banjo disrupt distillery VHS banh mi ugh et ut. Hella lo-fi nisi eiusmod fanny pack freegan. Cred tofu exercitation Marfa next level velit. Ennui do deep v sed messenger bag, elit flexitarian duis PBR&amp;amp;B vero American Apparel pork belly eu four loko. Selfies et nisi, magna paleo sriracha shabby chic Pitchfork vegan aute est.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Food truck meh dreamcatcher, semiotics scenester non keytar occupy. Craft beer tofu Odd Future, disrupt nisi food truck keffiyeh letterpress. Occaecat sed letterpress, locavore meggings wayfarers qui tattooed Carles Tumblr PBR asymmetrical slow-carb organic. Next level 90's nihil, try-hard gastropub Pitchfork butcher cornhole photo booth nisi sartorial odio ut occaecat. Voluptate pop-up keffiyeh kogi, artisan squid nihil VHS Thundercats accusamus mustache reprehenderit ad. Officia anim gastropub esse, flexitarian shabby chic Thundercats Echo Park American Apparel aute flannel Truffaut. Small batch voluptate kogi, semiotics wolf scenester Pinterest.&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://path-ghost-theme.rocketglow.com/raining-fire-in-the-sky/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">61635757-7c80-4290-9c9c-063a2d1b8fdf</guid><category>image</category><category>fire</category><category>sky</category><dc:creator>Chris Allen Moore</dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2014 10:56:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Welcome to Ghost</title><description>&lt;p&gt;You're live! Nice. We've put together a little post to introduce you to the Ghost editor and get you started. You can manage your content by signing in to the admin area at &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;your blog URL&amp;gt;/ghost/&lt;/code&gt;. When you arrive, you can select this post from a list on the left and see a preview of it on the right. Click the little pencil icon at the top of the preview to edit this post and read the next section!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="gettingstarted"&gt;Getting Started&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ghost uses something called Markdown for writing. Essentially, it's a shorthand way to manage your post formatting as you write!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Writing in Markdown is really easy. In the left hand panel of Ghost, you simply write as you normally would. Where appropriate, you can use &lt;em&gt;shortcuts&lt;/em&gt; to &lt;strong&gt;style&lt;/strong&gt; your content. For example, a list:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Item number one&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Item number two
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A nested item&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A final item&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;or with numbers!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remember to buy some milk  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drink the milk  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tweet that I remembered to buy the milk, and drank it&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3 id="links"&gt;Links&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Want to link to a source? No problem. If you paste in url, like &lt;a href="http://ghost.org/"&gt;http://ghost.org&lt;/a&gt; - it'll automatically be linked up. But if you want to customise your anchor text, you can do that too! Here's a link to &lt;a href="http://ghost.org/"&gt;the Ghost website&lt;/a&gt;. Neat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="whataboutimages"&gt;What about Images?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Images work too! Already know the URL of the image you want to include in your article? Simply paste it in like this to make it show up:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://ghost.org/images/ghost.png" alt="The Ghost Logo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not sure which image you want to use yet? That's ok too. Leave yourself a descriptive placeholder and keep writing. Come back later and drag and drop the image in to upload:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="quoting"&gt;Quoting&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes a link isn't enough, you want to quote someone on what they've said. It was probably very wisdomous. Is wisdomous a word? Find out in a future release when we introduce spellcheck! For now - it's definitely a word.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Wisdomous - it's definitely a word.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h3 id="workingwithcode"&gt;Working with Code&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Got a streak of geek? We've got you covered there, too. You can write inline &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;code&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; blocks really easily with back ticks. Want to show off something more comprehensive? 4 spaces of indentation gets you there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;.awesome-thing {
    display: block;
    width: 100%;
}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;h3 id="readyforabreak"&gt;Ready for a Break?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Throw 3 or more dashes down on any new line and you've got yourself a fancy new divider. Aw yeah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;h3 id="advancedusage"&gt;Advanced Usage&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There's one fantastic secret about Markdown. If you want, you can  write plain old HTML and it'll still work! Very flexible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;input type="text" placeholder="I'm an input field!"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That should be enough to get you started. Have fun - and let us know what you think :)&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://path-ghost-theme.rocketglow.com/welcome-to-ghost/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">200e0be9-1e27-4544-9b44-a0f6c991339a</guid><category>Getting Started</category><dc:creator>Chris Allen Moore</dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2014 09:57:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>